Guide to the Collège de la Sainte Famille Collection AD.MC.028
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- A street vendor on Khesro Street. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1985 (Object AD_MC_028_ref495)
  Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Street Vendors; Head Covers/Veils; Women; Outdoors; Men; Streets/Roads; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Priest with students. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1987 (Object AD_MC_028_ref496)
  Boys; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Students; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Children; Group Portraits
- Photo of a terrace on Mansour Street. 14 x 9 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref497)
  Arabic Writing; Buildings; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Houses
- A teacher chatting with a clergyman (Fr. Aldo Benetti) and the Vatican ambassador. 8.8 x 11.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref498)
  Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Men; Color Photography; Teachers; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- Son of the teacher beside him receiving an award for academic and sports achievement. 10.1 x 15 cm, 1985 (Object AD_MC_028_ref499)
  Color Photography; Arabic Writing; Head Covers/Veils; Women; Awards; Boys; Teachers; Schools/Education; Students; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions; Children; Facial Hair
- Student receiving an award. 8.9 x 12.7 cm, 26 February 1981 (Object AD_MC_028_ref500)
  Men; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Women; Awards; Teachers; Students; Boys; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Children; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions
- Students with a clergyman, one holds a trophy. 13.1 x 18 cm, 1962/63 (Object AD_MC_028_ref501)
  Schools/Education; Teachers; Uniforms; Priests/Clergymen; Boys; Students; Photographic Prints; Awards; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Children; Arabic Writing; Sports; Awards; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Trophy display at the school. 10.2 x 15.3 cm, 1987 (Object AD_MC_028_ref502)
  Schools/Education; Arabic Writing; Museums; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Group portrait of students with their teachers. 13.1 x 18 cm, 1962/1963 (Object AD_MC_028_ref503)
  Helwan, Egypt; Children; Parks; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Group Portraits; Boys; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Students; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education
- View of students lining up in the school playground. 11.9 x 17.9 cm, 1987 (Object AD_MC_028_ref504)
  Teachers; Boys; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits
- Students lining up and saluting in the school playground. 12.7 x 17.8 cm, 1987 (Object AD_MC_028_ref505)
  Helwan, Egypt; Children; Uniforms; Group Portraits; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Boys; Students; Photographic Prints
- Class photo. 11.6 x 16.7 cm, 1966 (Object AD_MC_028_ref506)
  Priests/Clergymen; Arabic Writing; Teachers; Men; Group Portraits; Students; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Children; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Class photo. 11.6 x 16.7 cm, 1966 (Object AD_MC_028_ref507)
  Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Children; Priests/Clergymen; Boys; Color Photography; Men; Teachers; Students; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Sixth grade school photo. 12.7 x 18 cm, 1982/83 (Object AD_MC_028_ref508)
  Women; Men; Teachers; Boys; Uniforms; Students; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Children
- Class photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref509)
  Women; Boys; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Group Portraits; Students; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Children; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- View of students lining up in the school playground. 12.7 x 17.7 cm, 1987 (Object AD_MC_028_ref510)
  Teachers; Schools/Education; Students; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Men; Boys; Color Photography; Group Portraits
- Group photo of teachers. 10.8 x 18.1 cm, 1987 (Object AD_MC_028_ref511)
  Group Portraits; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair
- Students behind fencing. 12.7 x 17.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref512)
  Students; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Children; Boys; Group Portraits
- Priest/teacher handing out trophies to students. 12.9 x 18 cm, 1962/63 (Object AD_MC_028_ref513)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Awards; Students; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Awards; Men; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Class photo. 12.7 x 18 cm, 1983/84 (Object AD_MC_028_ref514)
  Men; Women; Children; Color Photography; Boys; Students; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- Villa Aquilina at no. 28 Ragheb Street. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref515)
  Buildings; Color Photography; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Streets/Roads
- Class photo. 12.7 x 17.3 cm, 1977/78 (Object AD_MC_028_ref516)
  Schools/Education; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Women; Teachers; Children; Color Photography; Students; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair
- Class photo. 12.6 x 17.5 cm, 1977/78 (Object AD_MC_028_ref517)
  Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Children; Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Women; Teachers; Students; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
- Class photo. 12.7 x 17.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref518)
  Women; Men; Teachers; Color Photography; Students; Boys; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Children; Uniforms; Facial Hair
- Class photo. 12.7 x 17.7 cm, 1977 (Object AD_MC_028_ref519)
  Uniforms; Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boys; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Teachers; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Students; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Hats; Children
- Class photo. 12.7 x 17.2 cm, 1977/78 (Object AD_MC_028_ref520)
  Teachers; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Students; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Boys; Children; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Priests/Clergymen
- Class photo. 12.7 x 17.5 cm, 1969/1970 (Object AD_MC_028_ref521)
  Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Boys; Students; Children; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair
- Class photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref522)
  Uniforms; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Students; Schools/Education; Boys; Women; Teachers; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
- Sixth grade class photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, 1981 (Object AD_MC_028_ref523)
  Men; Women; Teachers; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Students; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Children; Color Photography; Priests/Clergymen; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Kindergarten class photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, 1983/84 (Object AD_MC_028_ref524)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Men; Women; Teachers; Kindergartens/Nurseries; Students; Schools/Education; Arabic Writing; Children; Boys; Facial Hair
- Class photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref525)
  Students; Priests/Clergymen; Schools/Education; Children; Group Portraits; Men; Women; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Color Photography; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Class photo. 12 x 17.7 cm, 1978 (Object AD_MC_028_ref526)
  Boys; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Men; Women; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Color Photography; Priests/Clergymen; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Pre-school class photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, 1983/84 (Object AD_MC_028_ref527)
  Children; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Students; Boys; Teachers; Women; Men; Group Portraits; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- First grade class photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref528)
  Color Photography; Group Portraits; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Children; Teachers; Schools/Education; Boys; Students; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Class photo. 11.4 x 15.7 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref529)
  Group Portraits; Men; Boys; Priests/Clergymen; Women; Children; Color Photography; Teachers; Students; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Class photo. 11.6 x 16.8 cm, 1969/70 (Object AD_MC_028_ref530)
  Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Color Photography; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Women; Teachers; Boys; Students
- Class photo. 11.4 x 16.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref531)
  Color Photography; Priests/Clergymen; Children; Men; Teachers; Students; Boys; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Class photo. 12.6 x 17.7 cm, 1977 (Object AD_MC_028_ref532)
  Men; Women; Teachers; Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- Class photo. 12.7 x 17.5 cm, 1977 (Object AD_MC_028_ref533)
  Children; Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Teachers; Group Portraits; Women; Boys; Students; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Priests/Clergymen; Facial Hair
- Scouts school photo. 12.7 x 17.5 cm, 1978 (Object AD_MC_028_ref534)
  Children; Group Portraits; Uniforms; Scouts; Men; Teachers; Students; Schools/Education; Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- 12th grade class portrait. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, 1983/84 (Object AD_MC_028_ref535)
  Group Portraits; Men; Teachers; Students; Boys; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Uniforms; Color Photography; Women; Schools/Education; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Children
- School photo of teachers. 12 x 17.8 cm, 1978 (Object AD_MC_028_ref536)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Teachers; Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Color Photography; Men; Schools/Education; Women; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Second grade class photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref537)
  Men; Schools/Education; Women; Children; Group Portraits; Teachers; Students; Boys; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Priests/Clergymen; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Class photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref538)
  Men; Teachers; Color Photography; Students; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Boys; Arabic Writing; Children; Group Portraits; Women; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- House on Ragheb Street. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref539)
  Color Photography; Street Lamps; Buildings; Cars/Trucks; Houses; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Transportation
- Eleventh grade class photo. 12.7 x 17.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref540)
  Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Boys; Color Photography; Men; Women; Teachers; Schools/Education; Students; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Uniforms; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Children
- A truck parked on the street. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref541)
  Buildings; Italian Writing; Cars/Trucks; Gelatin Silver Prints; Streets/Roads; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Transportation
- Entrance of a house. 14 x 9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref542)
  Arabic Writing; Houses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Doors/Entrances; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Entrance of a house on Mahmoud Khater Street. 14.1 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref543)
  Arabic Writing; Doors/Entrances; Houses; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- An ancient Egyptian cemetery in Ezbet El-Walda (tombs from I and II dynasties). 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref544)
  Men; Tombs/Mausoleums; Cemeteries; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Religious Sites; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Entrance of a house. 13 x 9.6 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref545)
  Architecture; Doors/Entrances; Houses; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
- House on Hussein Kamel Street. 14 x 9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref546)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Houses; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Doors/Entrances
- House on Riad Street. 14 x 9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref547)
  Doors/Entrances; Houses; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture
- A window of the Sacred Family church. 13.9 x 9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref548)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Churches; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Religious Sites
- House on Mustafa Fahmi Street. 9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref549)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Cars/Trucks; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Doors/Entrances; Houses; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints
- House on Mahmoud Khater Street. 9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref550)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Houses; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Wall detail. 9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref551)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- A well (?) on Mohammad Sayed Ahmad Street. 9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref552)
  Gardens; Water; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Fountains; Outdoors
- House on Heidar Street. 9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref553)
  Houses; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings
- Detail of an Art Nouveau balcony on Mahmoud Khater Street. 9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref554)
  Houses; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- House at no.43 Riad Street. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref555)
  Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Houses; Photographic Prints
- House on Mansour Street. 9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref556)
  Palm Trees; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Houses; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Al Tawfiki Mosque. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1986 (Object AD_MC_028_ref557)
  Religious Sites; Arabic Calligraphy; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- View of a house at no.39 Ragheb Street. 9.6 x 13 cm, 1975 (Object AD_MC_028_ref558)
  Houses; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Architecture
- Entrance of a house on Latif Street. 14 x 9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref559)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Doors/Entrances; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Doors/Entrances
- Balcony of a house on AbdelRahman Street. 13 x 8.9 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref560)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses
- Muslim graves in a village (Ezbat el-Babur). 7.4 x 13 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref561)
  Helwan, Egypt; Cemeteries; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Tombs/Mausoleums
- Apartment blocks in Helwan. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref562)
  Buildings; Landscapes; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Street Lamps
- No. 48 Zulfiqar Street, Helwan. 9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref563)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses
- The episcopio (Bishop's palace) in Helwan. 9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref564)
  Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Houses; Bicycles/Tricycles; Men; Religious Crosses; Helwan, Egypt; Palaces
- College of the Holy Family in Helwan. 13.8 x 9 cm, 1954 (Object AD_MC_028_ref565)
  Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing
- Helwan sanatorium. 9 x 14 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref566)
  Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Architecture; Sanitariums/Sanatoriums; Buildings; Hospitals; Photographic Prints
- 26 Street Ibrahim, Helwan. 9 x 14 cm., 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref567)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Streets/Roads; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Palm Trees; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture
- 22 Mohammed Said Ahmed Street, Helwan. 14 x 9 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref568)
  Streets/Roads; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt
- A building on Ismail Kamel street, Helwan. 9 x 14 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref569)
  Streets/Roads; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Electricity; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Architecture
- Building on Yousef Street, Helwan. 9 x 14 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref570)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Construction; Buildings; Houses
- The gardens of Ain Helwan sulfur baths. 9 x 13.8 cm, 1888 (Object AD_MC_028_ref571)
  Springs; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Outdoors; Palm Trees; Public Baths; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Uniforms; Landscapes
- Helwan sanatorium. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref572)
  Hospitals; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Architecture; Sanitariums/Sanatoriums; Streets/Roads; Palm Trees
- 17 Raghab Street, Helwan. 9 x 14 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref573)
  Houses; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Cars/Trucks; Gelatin Silver Prints
- College of the Holy Family. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref574)
  Italian Writing; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Streets/Roads; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
- Grand Hotel des Bains on Mansour Street, Helwan. 8.9 x 13 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref575)
  Buildings; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Hotels; Cars/Trucks; Transportation
- 28 Raghab Street, Helwan. 14 x 9 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref576)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses
- No. 16 Mahmoud Khater Street (demolished 1985). 14.1 x 9 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref577)
  Arabic Writing; Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Buildings; Houses; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- 36 Mahmoud Khater Street. 9 x 14 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref578)
  Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Houses; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Ibrahim Street in Helwan. 9 x 14 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref579)
  Men; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Houses; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Ex-Casino, Helwan. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref580)
  Casinos; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings
- Mosque on Latif Street. 12.8 x 8.2 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref581)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Architecture; Mosques; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Religious Sites
- House on Corniche Street. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref582)
  Architecture; Houses; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings
- House no. 12 on Onsi Street. 14 x 9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref583)
  Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Houses; Architecture; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints
- Pharaonic artifacts from Ezbet el-Walda. 9 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref584)
  Italian Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Mahmoud Khater Villa. 9 x 13.3 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref585)
  Outdoors; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Architecture; Italian Writing; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- No. 45 Burhan Street. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref586)
  Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Doors/Entrances; Buildings; Houses; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances
- A boarded up door on AbdelRahman Street. 8.9 x 12.2 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref587)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- 26 AbdelRahman Street. 14 x 9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref588)
  Houses; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Buildings; Architecture
- View of a street from above, with an Épicerie International in the foreground. 9 x 12 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref589)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Shops; Streets/Roads; Postcards; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Restaurants/bars; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings
- House 57 on Al Marsad Street. 9 x 14 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref590)
  Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Architecture; Houses; Italian Writing
- Helwan's Casino. 14 x 9 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref591)
  Buildings; Casinos; Doors/Entrances; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Signs/Signposts
- Entrance gates to a building in Helwan. 14 x 9 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref592)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Houses; Doors/Entrances
- Balcony at 28 Ragheb Street, Helwan. 9 x 14 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref593)
  Houses; Buildings; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- A postcard of a steam train. 9 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref594)
  Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Trains; Postcards; Photographic Prints; Transportation
- Postcard of an experimental locomotive equipped with Trevithick heaters. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref595)
  Arabic Writing; Trains; French Writing; Postcards; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Transportation; Machines; Palm Trees
- House entrance. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref596)